本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
诺斯维斯特  庄园
普雷斯顿  我得说
Preston, I must say,
今年宴会的宾客名单可真是异彩纷呈
the guest list for this year's party has so much diversity.
是啊  百万富翁和亿万富翁的绝妙搭配
Yes, a nice mix of millionaires and billionaires.
注意摆牡蛎叉的角度
Put the oyster fork at an angle.
我们可不是野兽
We're not animals, man.
细节决定成败
Now where the devil is...
帕西菲卡
Pacifica!
我是怎么跟你说裙子来着
What did I tell you about that dress?
这次主题是海绿色  不是湖绿色
The theme is sea foam green, not lake foam green.
-去换  -可我挺喜欢的
- Go change. - But I kind of like it.
听你母亲的话  帕西菲卡
Mind your mother, Pacifica.
但是
But--
好吧  父亲
Yes, Father.
糟糕  出现了
Oh, no, it's... happening.
听着  你是我的奴仆
Yes, you are my possessions.
服从我
Obey me!
这简直是个灾难
This is a disaster.
宴会一天之内就要开始了
The party's in just 24 hours.
一定有人可以处理这种混乱的局面
Surely there's someone who could handle this sort of nonsense.
我大概知道该找谁了
And I think I know just the person.
“解谜者”抓获吸血鬼蝙蝠
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
翻译： 阿拱  Peace.  战忽局副局座
时间轴  校订： Enpistu  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第二季第十集
Gravity Falls  S02E10  Northwest Mansion Mystery
■
后期： Enpistu  四通利方
我们满足大家的愿望
You asked for it, you got it.
整整四十八小时《捉鬼骚动队》节目连播
An entire 48-hour marathon of  Ghost Harassers.
即将在前历史频道播出
On the Used To Be About History Channel.
坚持住  小膀胱
Be strong, bladder.
得日落以后才能动弹呢
We're not gonna move till sunset.
紧急插播一条爆炸性新闻
We interrupt this program to bring you breaking news.
-什么  -开始啦
- Oh, what? - It's starting!
-大点声  -给格兰达挪个位置
- Turn it up. - Make room for Grenda.
我已经在这儿蹲守好几天了  只等今晚
Tonight's the night, but I've been out here for days.
诺斯维斯特观察
将在这里举行的诺斯维斯特家族
The Northwest family's annual
一年一度的上流豪华宴会
high-society shindig ball soiree is here.
尽管普通人不得进入
And even though common folk aren't let in,
但也无法阻止我们在外边安营扎寨
that won't stop us from camping out
只为一睹宴会的风采
for a peek at the fanciness.
好吧  谁能解释下为什么大家都关心这事儿
Okay, can someone please explain why people care about this?
这大概是有史以来最棒的宴会
Um, it's pretty much the best party of all time.
丰盛的食物  富家公子哥
Rich food, richer boys.
据说每个礼品篮里都有一只活鹌鹑
They say each gift basket has a live quail inside.
我想过你的人生  帕西菲卡
Give me your life, Pacifica.
伙计们  你们不要忘了
Guys, in case you've already forgotten,
帕西菲卡・诺斯维斯特这人差劲透了
Pacifica Northwest is the worst.
可不是因为嫉妒在背后说她坏话
And that's not just jealousy talking.
当着她的面我照说不误
I'd say that to her face.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
你差劲透了
You're the worst.
瞧见没
See?
听着  你以为我来这儿很容易么
Look, you think it's easy for me to come here?
我可不想被别人看到来这个破房子
I don't wanna be seen in this hovel.
可是诺斯维斯特庄园闹鬼了
But there's something haunting Northwest Manor.
如果你不帮我  宴会就会毁了
If you don't help me, the party could be ruined.
我凭什么相信你
And why should I trust you?
你所做的一切无非就是羞辱我和梅宝
All you've ever done is try to humiliate me and Mabel.
你开个价好了
Just name your price, okay?
我可以满足你任何要求
I'll give you anything.
嗨帕西菲卡  失陪一下
Hi, Pacifica. Excuse us.
迪普  你不明白这意味着什么吗
Dipper, don't you see what this means?
如果你帮了帕西菲卡  我们就可以参加
If you help Pacifica, you could get us invites
史上最盛大的宴会了
to the greatest party of all time.
什么  梅宝  我们说的可是帕西菲卡
What? Mabel, this is Pacifica we're talking about.
可这是糖糖和格兰达的梦想啊
But it's Candy and Grenda's dream.
梦想
Dream!
好吧  我帮你们抓鬼
Fine. I'll bust your ghost.
不过作为交换  我需要三张宴会入场券
But, in exchange, I'll need three tickets to the party.
算你走运  因为我现在急需帮助
You're just lucky I'm desperate.
哇  迫不及待  迫不及待  迫不及待
Whoo! Desperate, desperate, desperate!
格兰达  拿上胶枪  我们要做衣服啦
Grenda, get the glue gun. We're making dresses.
欢迎来到诺斯菲特宅邸  呆子们
Welcome to Northwest Manor, dorks.
别碰任何东西
Try not to touch anything.
一切都那么迷人
Everything's so fancy.
迷人的地板  迷人的植物
Fancy floors, fancy plants.
迷人的男子
Fancy man.
很好  小姐
Yes. Very good, miss.
传闻是真的哎
The rumors were true.
啊  这不是风云人物嘛
Ah, if it isn't the man of the hour.
但愿你能在客人们来之前
Hopefully, you can help us with our little... situation
-帮我们解决那个小问题  -我会尽力而为的
- before the guests arrive in an hour. - I'll do my best.
太好了  帕西菲卡  带我们的客人去那个出问题的房间
Splendid. Pacifica, take our guests to the problem room,
那个  他不会就穿那身吧
and, uh... he's not wearing that, is he?
我来解决
I'm on it.
这衣领要勒死我了
It's like this collar is strangling me.
你们穿这种东西是想给谁留下好印象
Who do you guys think you're impressing with this stuff?
每个人啊
Um, everyone.
你不会明白的
You wouldn't understand.
正是高标准成就了诺斯维斯特家族的伟大
High standards are what make the Northwest family great.
有趣儿  我还以为因为你们谎称创建了小镇呢
Funny, I thought it was lying about founding the town.
别碰那个
Don't touch that.
哇  伙计们  这是宾客名单
Oh, wow, guys, it's the guest list.
看看这个帅哥
Check out this hottie.
马吕斯・冯・昂斯豪泽
Marius von Fundshauser.
来自奥地利的男爵
He's a baron from Austria.
别管鹌鹑了  我要把他放进我的礼物篮里去
Forget the quail. I'm putting him in my guest basket.
等会儿  女士们  真不敢相信我会这样说
Hold up, ladies. I can't believe I'm gonna say this,
可我觉得这男孩我们高攀不起
but I think this boy is out of our league.
格兰达说的对  他是触不可及的男神
Grenda's right. He's a white whale.
追求他会毁掉我们的友谊的
Hunting him will destroy us.
还会有超多的可爱男生来呢
There are tons of cute boys coming.
我们设个姐妹协定吧  不在马吕斯身上花时间
Let's swear a sisters' truce not to waste time on Marius.
同意
Deal.
-同意  -说定了
- Deal. - Deal.
这是那个出问题的主厅
This is the main room where it's been happening.
嗯  看上去就像那种会闹鬼的房间
Yep, this looks like the kind of room that would be haunted, all right.
不过我可不担心
I wouldn't be worried, though.
第十类
高危！
鬼怪按介绍分成十类
Ghosts fall under a ten-category scale.
盘子掉落应该是第一类
Falling plates sound like a category one.
第一类
切。
那又怎样  你该不会打算读这本书来烦鬼怪
So what? Are you going to bore him back into the afterlife
把他们赶回阴间吧
by reading from this book?
只要把圣水洒到那些家伙身上
Just gotta splash this sucker with some anointed water,
他们就会离开你那八成是染色的金发了
and he should be out of your probably-fake blonde hair.
你说我头发怎么了
What was that about my hair?
嘘  侦测到东西了
Sh. I'm picking something up.
拜托  蠢东西  这才对
Come on, stupid thing. There we go.
帕西菲卡
Uh, Pacifica?
古老的罪恶  古老的罪恶
Ancient sins. Ancient sins.
迪普  这是什么情况
Dipper, what is this?
这属于第十类
It's a category ten.
古老之血  暗黑天空
Ancient blood and blackened skies.
黑暗森林  东山再起
The forest dark shall once more rise.
我们该怎么办  怎么办啊
What do we do, what do we do?
别担心  情况至少不会更糟了
Don't worry. It can't get worse than this.
我闻到了一个姓诺斯维斯特的
I smell a Northwest.
出来
Come out.
不管你在哪儿  出来
Come out, wherever you are.
快点  快翻你那本蠢书
Hurry. Read through your dumb book already.
我正在找  而且这书一点也不蠢好吗
I'm looking, and it's not dumb, okay?
这本书能救我们的命
This book is gonna save our lives.
找到了  在这儿  建议
All right, here we go. Advice.
自求多福！
有没有搞错
Oh, seriously?
你不应该来这里
You shouldn't have come here.
这边  快
This way. Hurry!
欢迎光临  公爵和公爵夫人们
Welcome, dukes and duchesses.
苏丹们和运动员们
Sultans and sportsmen.
呦  近来可好  普莱斯托
Yo, what up, Presto?
还有重力泉深居简出的一百零二岁市长
And reclusive 102-year-old mayor of Gravity Falls,
比法弗托法普特尔镇长
Mayor Befufftlefumpter.
没事儿  它们是跟我一起的
It's okay. They're with me.
今夜  我们将会品尝到最美味的食物
Tonight, we will enjoy only the finest of tastes
享受最高贵的欢乐
and only the snootiest of laughter.
那就是入场券
That's the ticket.
奶酪  巧克力
Cheese, chocolate.
糖糖  仔细听我说
Candy, listen to me carefully.
你陷入了一个香甜怪圈
You're caught in a sweet-savory loop.
快把火锅叉放下
Put the fondue fork down.
我想  但我做不到
I want to, but I can't.
有请男爵马吕斯・冯・昂斯豪泽
Introducing Baron Marius von Fundshauser.
你好
Guten tag.
好呀  现在就带我走
Guten take me now!
梅宝  我们有姐妹协定
Mabel, we had a truce.
对  对  对  姐妹协定
Yes, yes, yes, a truce.
格兰达  你能帮我们去拿一些漂亮的餐巾纸吗
Grenda, can you go fetch us some fancy napkins?
哇  好哒
Wow. Okay.
听着  梅宝  我不知道能不能守得住这个协定
Listen, Mabel, I don't know if I can follow this truce.
-他太可爱了  -我也这么觉得  糖糖
- He is too adorable. - Me, too, Candy.
但我们又能怎么办呢  他触不可及
But what do we do? He's unattainable.
假如我们组队与他调情会怎么样呢
What if we flirt with him as a team?
把我们的可爱力量联合起来  也许其中一个就会有机会
With our cuteness combined, one of us might have a chance.
这是个完美的计划
It is the perfect plan.
但格兰达怎么办
But what about Grenda?
我爱格兰达  梅宝  但这些男孩儿都很精致
I love Grenda, Mabel, but these boys are fancy.
她侵略性的调情风格可能会吓跑人家的
Her aggressive flirting style might scare them away.
嘿  你衣服上是啥
Hey, what's on your shirt?
哈  上当了  笨蛋
Ha! Gullible! Loser!
快  穿过花园
Hurry. Through the garden.
小心孔雀
Watch out for peacocks.
快点  快点  我找到了
Come on, come on. I got it.
只有用银镜才能捕获画中幽灵
A haunted painting can only be trapped in a silver mirror.
看  那里就有一面银镜
Look, there's a silver mirror right there.
等等  不能进去
Wait. Don't go in there.
这个房间的地毯是我父母最喜欢的
This room has my parents' favorite carpet pattern.
如果把泥巴踩进去他们会气疯的
They'll lose it if we track mud in there.
什么  你有没有搞错
What? Are you serious?
我们想其他办法吧
We'll find another way.
帕西菲卡  我们没时间了  让我过去
Pacifica, we don't have time for this. Let me through!
不  我父母会杀了我
No. My parents will kill me.
你为什么那么怕你父母
Why are you so afraid of your parents?
你是不会明白的
You wouldn't understand.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
好奇怪  我都不知道这个房间在哪儿
That's weird. I don't even know where this room is.
希望那幽灵也不知道
Hopefully, the ghost doesn't either.
对  我们大概安全了
Yeah. Maybe we're safe.
帕西菲卡  小心
Pacifica! Watch out!
你的命运被封印了
Your fate is sealed!
银镜子
A silver mirror.
受死吧  诺斯维斯特
Prepare to die, Northwest!
你抓到他了吗
Did you get him?
放我出去
Oh, free me!
好耶
Yes!
我们成功了
We did it!
我给你钱  装作刚才什么也没发生好吗
Can I pay you to pretend that never happened?
帕西菲卡  你找他来做这份工作真是再合适不过了
Well, Pacifica, you really found the right man for the job.
我们感激不尽
We can't thank you enough.
够了
That's enough.
嘿  我只是按照约定做事而已
Hey, just holdin' up my end of the deal.
等等  你这就要走
Wait. Leaving already?
你现在可是身处世上最棒的宴会啊  傻瓜
You're at the world's best party, dummy.
我也想留下来
I'd love to stay,
但我还有个第十类的鬼怪要处理
but I've got a category ten ghost to dispose of.
哈哈  第十类
Ha ha. Category ten.
我可能是疯了
Call me crazy,
但她可能也没那么坏
but maybe she's not that bad after all.
你在笑什么  老头儿  我打败了你
What are you laughing about, man? I defeated you.
你中招了  孩子
You've been had, boy.
你让我想起一百五十年前的自己
You remind me of me 150 years ago.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
一百五十年前的今天
One hundred and fifty years ago this day,
诺斯维斯特家族让我们伐木工人
the Northwests asked us lumber folk
在山顶为他们建造一幢豪宅
to build them a mansion atop the hill.
还告诉我们这将用于为全镇人服务
We were told it would be a service to the town,
他们将每年举行一次盛大的宴会
that once a year, they would throw
而且人人都可以享受这份福利
a grand party, and all would share in the bounty.
我们为此付出了多年的劳苦和牺牲
It took years of back-breaking labor and sacrifice,
但当盛大的宴会举行之时
but when it was time for the grand party
曾经向镇上普通平民作出承诺的他们
they promised the common folk of the town,
却拒绝我们入内
they refused to let us in.
你承诺过的  诺斯维斯特
You promised, Northwest.
由于树木被砍伐  泥石流爆发了
With the trees gone, the mudslides began.
当他们笑语欢歌之时
While they partied and laughed,
我被泥石流卷走
I was swept away by the storm.
我用尽最后一口气发下诅咒
And so I said with final breath,
一百五十年后我将起死回生
150 years I'll return from death.
若这大门仍向小镇关闭
And if the gate still closed to town,
富人之血将沾污大地
wealthy blood will stain the ground.
当心  伐木工的诅咒
这个诅咒一直传至今日
A curse passed down until this day.
所以等一下
So wait a minute.
诺斯维斯特家族知道这次闹鬼事件会发生
The Northwests knew this haunting was coming,
他们骗我帮忙是为了
and they tricked me into helping them
逃避鬼魂的裁决  我马上回来
to avoid ghostly justice? I'll be right back.
感谢您的光临  镇长
Thank you so much for coming, mayor.
小小敬意  请笑纳这只黑猩猩仆人
As a sign of our respect, please take this chimp servant.
不要让他靠近繁华的花花世界
Keep him away from bright lights.
他会变得贪婪
He gets grabby.
诺斯维斯特家的
Northwests!
你们给我解释一下
You've got some explaining to do.
迪普  你回来了
Dipper, you came back.
你骗了我  你们全家都一样
You lied to me. All of you did.
你们只需要让镇里的居民参加宴会
All you had to do was let the townsfolk into the party,
就可以破除诅咒
and you could've broken the curse.
但你却让我替你们完成这肮脏的勾当
But you made me do your dirty work instead.
看看你在跟谁说话  孩子
Look at who you're talking to, boy.
我正为这个世界上最有权势的人们举办着宴会
I'm hosting a party for the most powerful people in the world.
如果还得跟你这种人打交道  你觉得他们还会来吗
You think they'd come here if they had to rub elbows with your kind?
我这种人
My kind?
我对你的看法一直都没错
I was right about you all along.
你和你父母一样坏
You're just as bad as your parents.
是这个世界上败类链条中的一环
Another link in the world's worst chain.
对不起  他们逼我的
I'm sorry. They made me.
我本应该告诉你  但
I should've told you, but...
好好享受宴会  这是你这种人最后一次来这里
Enjoy the party. It's the last time you and your kind will ever come.
不  不  那不是给他的
No, no! Those aren't for him.
混蛋诺斯维斯特家族
Stupid Northwests.
让我替他们驱鬼
Making me do their exorcism for them.
恶灵退散  收摄不祥
Exodus demonus, spookus scarus,
超汝孤魂  何鬼敢当
aintafraidus noghostus.
迪普  请让我报复诺斯维斯特家族
Dipper, please let me get my vengeance on the Northwests.
你和我一样恨他们
You hate them as much as I.
嘿  我感同身受
Hey, I feel you.
只是我姐姐在里面
It's just, my sister's in there,
而且你看起来精神不太稳定啊  老头儿
and you seem a little unstable, man.
很好  孩子
Very well, boy.
那在你驱逐我的灵魂之前
Then before you banish my soul,
能让我衰老的伐木之眼
may these tired old lumber eyes
最后再凝望一次树林吗
gaze upon the trees one final time?
呃  行吧
Uh... I guess.
看吧  老头儿
Go nuts, man.
什么
What?
太好啦  复仇
Yes! Vengeance!
哦  不  梅宝
Oh, no. Mabel!
嗨  我是梅宝
Hi. I'm Mabel.
你是澳大利亚人哈
So, Australia, huh?
你们那儿吃袋鼠肉吗
Do you guys eat kangaroo meat over there,
还是只把它们当宠物养
or are they strictly pets?
我来自奥地利
I am from Austria.
传给你
Tag, tag.
我是糖糖
I am Candy.
我喜欢你肩上的小帽子
I love the tiny hats you wear on your shoulders.
如果你是一艘船  知道你会是哪种吗
If you were a boat, do you know what kind you'd be?
梦之船  就是那种
A dreamboat. That's what kind.
-你出局了  -我又回来了
- You're tagged out. - Tagged back in.
-你不能这样  -我可以传回自己的  不犯规
- You can't do that. - I can tag myself. It's allowed.
你们怎么能这样对我
What exactly was all that?
居然抛下我和马吕斯调情
You were flirting with Marius without me.
对不起  格兰达  只不过
We're sorry, Grenda. It's just...
你调情的风格有那么点  太过了
Your flirting style can come off as a bit... intense.
我算是知道了
Oh, I see.
你觉得我来到这栋愚蠢的豪宅里
You think I shouldn't be myself
就不该表现真实的自我了
just because I'm in this stupid mansion.
我还以为你们喜欢我的风格呢
I thought you liked my style.
我们倒是喜欢  可这群帅哥就不一定了
We do, but these boys might not.
那他们肯定也不会喜欢这个的
Then I guess they wouldn't like this either.
-喂  马吕斯  -怎么了
- Hey, Marius. - Yeah?
你衣服上有东西
You've got something on your shirt.
多谢各位的光临
Thank you all for coming.
看来今晚的宴会举办得圆满成功
I think we can all say this party was a rousing success.
圆满得就像大灌篮一样  普雷斯顿
I guess you could say it was a slam dunk, Preston.
对  对  你说得挺好的
Yes, yes, I guess, sure.
请举杯  向我们的家族致意
A toast... to our family name.
怎么回事
What?!
封印了百年时光
Generations locked away.
是时候血债血偿
My revenge shall have its day.
哟  这不是死神嘛
Oh, the Grim Reaper.
我还以为你都把我忘了
I've been wondering when you would arrive.
普雷斯顿  我们该怎么办
Preston, what are we going to do?
准备好避难室
Prepare the panic room.
求求你  救命啊
Please... help me.
哎呀  这可真是一团糟
Whoa! That is messed up.
扭转命运一线生机犹存
Just one way to change your fates.
诺斯维斯特必须亲自敞开大门
A Northwest must open the party gates.
诺斯维斯特  帕西菲卡
A Northwest? Pacifica.
帕西菲卡  你在这里啊
Pacifica. There you are.
那幽灵把大家都变成木雕了
The ghost is turning everyone to wood,
说话还莫名其妙地押起了韵
and he just started rhyming for some reason.
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
帕西菲卡
Pacifica?
想知道为什么这个房间被锁住了吗
Wanna know why this room was locked up?
看看我都发现了什么
This is what I found in here.
这些画纪录了我的家族
A painted record of every
做过的每一件可怕的事情
horrible thing that my family's ever done.
他们鬼话连篇  信口雌黄  再往后就到我了
Lying, cheating, and then, there's me.
我跟你撒谎是因为
I lied to you just because I'm
我不敢跟我那愚蠢的父母做对
too scared to talk back to my stupid parents.
你说得没错
You were right about me.
我只是这个世界败类链条上的另一环而已
I am just another link in the world's worst chain.
帕西菲卡  之前我说气话  实在是对不起
Pacifica, I'm sorry about what I said earlier,
但你虽然身为他们的女儿
but just because you're your parents' daughter
并不意味着一定要步你父母的后尘
doesn't mean you have to be like them.
现在还来得及
It's not too late.
-已经太迟了  -糟了
- It's too late! - Oh, no!
你们都成木头了
You are all wood!
迪普  等等
Dipper, wait.
看好了  幽灵
All right, ghost.
你就准备
Prepare to get...
别  等等
No, wait!
惨了  惨了  惨了
No, no, no, no!
不  来人啊  救命啊
No, someone help. Someone help!
满园的木头人  都把教训收好
A forest of death, a lesson learned.
诺斯维斯特庄园即将被大火焚烧
And now, the Northwest manor will burn!
哎  丑八怪
Hey, ugly.
我在这儿呢
Over here.
你想让我把镇里人都请来吗
You want me to let in the townsfolk?
我说到做到
'Cause I'll do it.
把大家都变回来吧
Just change everyone back.
想要证明你自己吗
You wish to prove yourself?
拉下操纵杆  把大门向全镇敞开
Pull that lever and open the grand gate to the town.
大门
实现你祖先的承诺吧
Fulfill your ancestors' promise.
帕西菲卡・伊莉斯・诺斯维斯特
Pacifica Elise Northwest,
马上停下来
stop this instant.
怎么能让全镇的人看到我们这个样子
We can't let the town see us like this.
我们必须要保住贵族的声望
We have a reputation to uphold.
快来避难室避难吧
Now come into the panic room.
这里的三明治和氧气
There's enough mini sandwiches and oxygen
够供应咱们和管家活一个星期
to last you, me, and a butler for a week.
我们要把管家吃了
We'll eat the butler.
你胆敢违背我们
You dare disobey us?
没听到铃声在叮叮响吗
Dingly, dingly. Is this bell broken?
我们家族早就身名俱裂了
Our family name is broken,
我要把它修正过来
and I'm gonna fix it.
快打开  快打开
Get it, get it.
好  好  终于实现了
Yes, yes, it's happening.
我坚如橡木的心啊
My heart, once as hard as oak,
现在软化得像藤条什么的
now grows soft like more of a birch or something.
帕西菲卡  你和你的家人很不一样
Pacifica, you are not like the other Northwests.
我的灵魂可以安息了
I feel lumber justice.
好啊  哈哈
Oh, yes! Yeah!
老天爷啊  乡巴佬都来了
Good Lord, the riff-raff.
到处都是乡巴佬
They're everywhere.
叉子怎么能这样乱放呢
That's not how the fork should be placed.
呃  到底发生了什么
Ugh, man, what happened?
格兰达  真是对不起
Grenda, we are so sorry.
我们不该背着你去找帅哥的
We shouldn't have left you behind.
没关系的
It's okay.
我调情的水平还是有待提高啊
Maybe I do need to work on my flirting.
走  快去奶酪巧克力里泡泡脑袋吧
Come on, let's go dunk our heads into cheese and chocolate.
-还是好闺蜜  -好闺蜜
- Friends. - Friends.
等等  请留步
Wait! Don't go.
你是叫格兰达吧  我必须跟你谈谈
Grenda, was it? I must speak with you.
你确实有特殊之处
There's something about you.
让我魂牵梦萦的
I can't get you out of my head.
你那么大胆  那么自信
You're so bold and confident.
尽管咱们不在同一个阶层
I know you're probably out of my league,
但你可以接受我的手机号吗
but might I give you mein phone number?
我连手机都没有
I don't have a phone.
写我脸上得了
Write it on my face.
格兰达  了不起哟
Whoa! Go, Grenda.
看来我们真把她看扁了
I guess we shouldn't have sold her short.
我要当伴娘
I call bridesmaid.
什么  那我就是伴娘二号
What? I call co-bridesmaids.
天啊  如果你父母为这事怨你的话
Man, if your family hates you for this,
那就是脑袋不灵光了  宴会太赞了
they're idiots. This is great.
好好享受吧
Enjoy it while it lasts.
明年这时候  他们肯定又把大家关在门外了
Next year, I'm sure they're just gonna lock everyone out again.
哎  看看我们脚底下
Hey, guess what we're standing on.
看我的
Take that.
玩归玩  我还得找人把这儿清理干净
But seriously, I'd better go find someone to clean this up.
当哩个当  俺的老寒腿啊颤呀么颤
Whoo! Scoobiddy doo! Hornswaggle my goat knees!
麦戈科特  别来无恙啊
Well, ho-ho, what's up, McGucket?
迪普  我找你找了好久
Dipper, I been lookin' for you.
我把电脑修好了
I fixed the laptop.
我做了大量的计算工作
I've been doin' calculations,
推测出有件可怕的事要来了
and I think something terrible is comin'.
世界末日  世界终结
The apocalypse. The end times.
麦戈科特  你猜怎么着
You know what, McGucket.
这件事咱们改日再说吧
How about we talk about this stuff tomorrow?
这可是个宴会  好好玩玩不行吗
It's a party. Let's have some fun for once, huh?
这下可糟糕了
Oh, this is bad.
紧迫威胁
时间马上就到了
Somethin's comin'.
大事就要发生了
Somethin' big.
亲爱的  快跟我来这儿
Quick, in here, my darling.
总算没外人了
A moment alone at last.
特雷格  你别再演了
You can drop the act, Trigger.
他们发现机器有动静了
They're seeing activity on the machine.
-开始行动  -收到指示
- It's go time. - Roger that.
我的手机在哪儿
Where's my phone?
-不在我身上  -谁说的  就在你手袋里
- I don't have it. - Yes, you do. It was in your purse.
看样子我还得帮你带这带那
So I'm just supposed to hold onto everything for you?
在车里不是都说好了吗
I asked you when we were in the car.
怎么每到宴会我们就得掐架
Why do we always have to fight at parties?
不打扰你们的雅兴
Not even gonna ask.